

Daniyal Khan

REACT DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

For the past 6 years, my passion for web development has driven me to acquire extensive knowledge. During this time, I successfully developed two commercial websites and actively contributed to Pakistan's largest charity, the Edhi Foundation. Currently, I am immersed in exploring React to enhance my skill set and stay at the forefront of web development innovations

EXPERIENCE

April 2023 - September 2023

Website Manager

SS Classes / India, Mumbai

Website manager for an educational firm, adept at handling vast data. Proven manager, skillfully navigating responsibilities with composure, ensuring everything runs smoothly. Expert in making it all look good

October 2023 - Now

Frontend Developer

Techno Serve Software Solutions / India, Mumbai

Built multiple commercial websites, contributed to Edhi Foundation's frontend, and diving deeper into React. Passionate about enhancing web experiences. Committed to continuous learning for impactful applications and aesthetic design

EDUCATION

• 2019 - 2020

SSC

Al- Ittehad Urdu High School / India, Mumbai

I completed my Secondary School Certificate (SSC) education at Al Ittehad Urdu High School, where I received a well-rounded education that prepared me for higher studies and personal growth.

• 2021 - 2022

HSC

Rizvi College Of Arts Science & Commerce / India, Mumbai

During my time at Rizvi College of Arts, Science, and Commerce, I gained a thorough education in the Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC) program with a focus on Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics, and Biology (PCMB).

• 2022 - Now

Bachelor of Engineering

Rizvi College Of Engineering / India, Mumbai

During my Bachelor's in Computer Science at Rizvi College of Engineering, I learned programming languages, data structures, algorithms, software engineering, web development,. These subjects have prepared me for diverse roles in software development, IT, and research.

\mathscr{C}	07738875007
$oxed{\Box}$	daniyal733khan@gmail.com
0	India, Mumbai, Mumbai, 400102

https://edhiuk.org https://humanaidfoundation.org/ https://careandrelief.uk/ https://akmalhajjumrah.com/ https://banburymadnimasjid.com/

Web Development
Testing and Debugging
React JS
Next JS
Svelte + Astro
Teamwork
Time Management
Leadership

HOBBIES

SKILLS

- Learning JavaScript Frameworks
- Design and Prototyping
- Attending Meetups and Conferences